http://www.necaseattle.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentPrivacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs);To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature;To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please call the NECA office at 206-284-2150 and we will remove you from our mailing list.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.Do we use cookies?We do not use cookies.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy ProtectionBecause we value your privacy we will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on 01-08-2013.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Puget Sound Chapter, NECA10700 Meridian Ave N, #401Seattle, WA 98133USA206-284-2150www.necaseattle.org
